H035
ダーウィンとガラパゴス
H035  •  相関接続詞／従属接続詞／接続副詞
In 1831, Charles Darwin began a voyage around the
world aboard a British survey ship.
During the five years of that expedition, he visited
many islands along the coast of South America.
On the Galapagos Islands, he carefully observed how
animals varied from island to island.
He collected birds that were later identified in England
as related finch species with different beaks.
Darwin collected many specimens and, after his
return, spent long years in thought.
Why were there different animals on different islands?
Why had they adapted so perfectly to each
environment?
In 1859, the publication of his book, On the Origin of
Species, shook the world.
The concept of evolution shook the belief of the age.
Although there was fierce criticism, Darwin's theory,
over time, came to be accepted.
Nature, quietly yet deeply, continues to change from
generation to generation.